comparebusinessproducts.com 2014-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Reviews, Comparisons and Buyer’s Guides

[www.comparebusinessproducts.com](http://www.comparebusinessproducts.com/) (the SITE) is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the SITE and governs data collection and usage. By using the SITE, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

###  Collection of your Personal Information

Wheelhouse Enterprises, Inc, (the Company) collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. The Company also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by the Company. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by The Company for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the SITE.

###  Use of your Personal Information

The Company collects and uses your personal information to operate the SITE and deliver the services you have requested. The Company also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The Company and its affiliates. There are cases where your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties.

Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of the Company, on an anonymous basis. When you request information from the Company or one or more of our clients, we may transfer that information within the Company or route your information to our client(s) so that they may provide the information that you requested. In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that the Company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information.

The Company will disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The Company or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the SITE; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the SITE, or the public.

###  Use of Cookies

The SITE uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the SITE.

###  Security of your Personal Information

The Company secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The Company secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

###  Your California Privacy Rights

Beginning January 1, 2005, California passed legislation requiring certain disclosures be made available to California residents who use the Internet to provide information that may be used for marketing purposes. California residents may request information about whether the business has disclosed personally identifiable information to third parties and may also request that this information not be shared. If you are a California resident, you may request this at the address below.

###  Children

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Focus Research, Inc. websites are not directed at children less than thirteen years of age, and the Company does not intend to collect personally identifiable information from such individuals.

###  Changes to this Statement

The Company will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The Company encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how The Company is protecting your information.

###  Contact Information

The Company welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The Company has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The Company at:

###  Wheelhouse Enterprises, Inc

1730 S. Amphlett Blvd., Ste. 101  
San Mateo, CA 94402  
650-681-9888
